Parisa Kashisaz

Java Developer

parisakashisaz1@gmail.com

+98 09392971147

• Tehran, Iran

S live:.cid.4bedbcaf614c60c7

15/08/2001

in www.linkedin.com/in/parisa-kashisaz-b52366262

PROFILE

I started learning Java Spring Boot programming at Fakour Academy and after 3 months I managed to finish the course and received my certification. Soon after I was hired by Fakour Company and I start worked professionally in the field of back-end programming. Iam very interested in learning and overcoming new challenges. I can work effectively as part of a team and my colleagues know me as a good player at team.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

03/2024 - present Tehran, Iran

Dotin

java developer

- · Participated in the development and implementation of foreign exchange credit processes within the core banking system, gaining comprehensive knowledge of various international financial instruments and banking operations such as letter of credits (LC), bills, forex sales transactions, and cross-currency trades using Java Core and Spring Framework stack.
- Worked with relational databases such as Oracle and PostgreSQL to design and implement data models aligned with business requirements and domain-driven design principles.
- · Utilized modern development tools including Swagger for API documentation and JHipster for application scaffolding during microservices-based development.
- Developed and implemented Samtak-related business logic for credit workflows using Spring and Java Core, including message generation, management, transmission, and integration with the Central Bank system.

06/2023 - 10/2023 Tehran, Iran

IPAAM Fintech

Java developer

- Working with Camunda and develop different features in the banking processes
- · Working with Spring Security and defining roles and permissions for users
- Experience working with Oracle database

10/2021 - 05/2023 Tehran, Iran

Fakour

Junior Java developer

- · Working as a junior Java developer in discovery and alarm management and asset manager modules and learning about telecommunication networks
- A superficial experience of working with Kafka
- · Storing all network elements with hierarchy and complex relationships in the graph database (Neo4j)

EDUCATION

10/2022 - 07/2024 Tehran, Iran

Bachelor's Software Engineering

Azad University

10/2019 - 06/2021 Tehran, Iran

Associate Software Engineering

Azad University

SKILLS

Spring-Boot | Spring-Security | Spring-Data | Java | JPA | OOP | MVC | Maven | SOLID Principle | Hibernate | Neo4j | Oracle | Postgre | JHipster | Git | Camunda | kafka | Swagger | Jira | Agile

O LANGUAGES

Speaks Persian as a native tongue

● ● ● English

• • • •